hello hello hello hello hello hello hello hello hello welcome to another edition of
hello marvel patch um welcome to another edition or should i say shada shada raja
dawn dawn king another edition of what would your ancestors say so we've been doing this every night
um giving folks the opportunity to come on my instagram live and talk about their ancestry
talk about where they think they came from where they know they came from to talk about what they
think their ancestors would say about where we are about where we're going and um you know maybe
also what they think their answers would say about where they are and um if you want to get my thoughts
on the use of white house funds for remodeling you can check out the latest episode of views
from amanda land which is now available on youtube amanda seals tv okay um and so want to remind you
all that my book is over there want to remind you all that my book what would the ancestors say
is available uh as part of the tickets for my live stream of the show what would the ancestors say
which is happening on november 8th so hopefully you guys will support and i'll be coming to a city near
you doing a book signing tour uh with a book talk so hopefully you guys hey beetle hope you guys you
guys will be able to come through those cities as well if you cannot watch the live stream but i
appreciate everybody who's been going to amanda seals.com and purchasing their live stream ticket
purchasing their live stream tickets um and purchasing um their in-studio tickets as well because
anybody who is in la you will be able to actually come to the taping itself of what would the ancestors
say and that is going to be happening on november 8th okay so this run i'm not i see people asking
about colorado about phoenix i'm actually not coming to colorado and phoenix on this run however in the
spring i will come back out into the streets um and of course depending on where the people are
where the world is at that time will definitely have an effect on where i go and i also want to tell
you all that one of the things i'm working on is that when i do my book tour stops i want to be
partnering with organizations to do different drives in different cities i know some places
they really need to get support with food for food pantries um other places it may be more about the
winter is coming and doing cloak sorry coat drives and blanket drives and sleeping bag drives etc
so regardless i am always thinking of how can i use the spaces that i am in to expand um you know the
information base of mutual aid so that's something that i'm always doing um this person true to you
uh we do not share the same belief system about ancestry so this is either going to be pointless
for you or it's going to be useful for you to expand your mind but i want you to know that this mindset
nothing the dead knows nothing seven exclamation points is not welcome here so someone said my show
was on so um you can go right here in to the see this little camera icon right here you can go here
and um you can go right here and hold on one second why is this not letting me go online and um request
to come on in the meantime in between time let me show y'all a little bit about what what would the
ancestors say is all uh bam hold on okay why can't i find what i'm looking for y'all here we go
why is there no sound can you hear is there sound interesting please see these corporations like oh my
god why is there no sound i'm in a weird mood if you're interested so you know here's the thing about
what would the ancestors say that i didn't realize until i got the book is that i feel like i created
a new genre i feel like i created a new genre because yes the performance is its own thing
but in text form i feel like when people ask me like oh you should write essays like i don't i don't
want to do that i don't like writing essays like it actually feels like school in a bad way and i
actually was really good at school um but what this book has opened for me what this has actually
broken open for me is like a way to bring in academic and scholarship academia and scholarship
intellectualism and philosophy into um
um a space of literature that is unhindered so within this book like there's poetry there's monologues
there's characters there's dialogue and there's lecture and
i feel like that to me feels so organic to how i think as an artistic intellectual
intellectualism because it's not in a finite way um i'm not somebody that that looks at myself and
says like oh like i'm a i'm a um historian or whatever i'm just a
per i'm like a high vibrational person in the world
so oh thanks pyc pretty young someone says are you doing any community projects to follow up with
what you're learning i am a community project i literally exist as a community project sometimes
i wonder sometimes i wonder kind of like what you guys mean when you ask questions like that
like we're sitting here like we're sitting here on instagram live
this is my third night in a row
doing this giving people space to talk about their ancestry
this is a community project i think we don't we don't acknowledge enough
of how artistic spaces
are integral parts
of community
upliftment
mutual aid etc don't get me wrong we also need the other mutual aid right we need the food
we need
the funds
we also like kimmy said right here like we have to teach the babies and for what it's worth when we say
teach the babies that's also y'all that's us
if any anybody who works with adults knows it's working with children
am i lying anybody who works with adults knows that you're you're working with children
adults are actually harder kids to work with than kids
okay
um so when people say things like are you doing community projects i don't know
how that's not evident
also because what we also have to understand is that the concept of community
community has also evolved right so like we have people on here that are all over the world
we have folks in scotland we have folks in cali we have folks in who else is in here i know we got
somebody in london in here who's who's up late
um so the concept of community is also different views from amanda land is a community project
views from amanda land is a free show that i do every wednesday on youtube amanda seals tv
we have oh we have mexico in here we have australia in here we have kansas in here
we have another australia in here new york morocco is in here okay so on views from amanda land
we have all of these people who join every wednesday and if they can't join live they re-watch
and they re-watch and they take pride in being part of the re-watch
and they contribute in their earnestness to be a part of the community also in how they interact
in the algorithm i mean how they interact in the um comment section and then people who have
subscribed to my patreon which is five dollars a month they go after the show and have a whole zoom
for hours hours these are all spaces that are community what would the ancestors say i did
five free shows of what would the ancestors say over the course of this year at the people's forum
and in the last in the case of the last show that i did there people were able to reserve their seat
with a donation to the people's forum so if you're wondering what are the community projects
i exist constantly in a community project i also just talked about how when i'm on my book tour
i will be doing what i used to do on my stand-up tours which is bring people from organizations that
are working in those communities to come and talk about the work that they're doing and also to
to partner with me to do drives okay so um we are about to just so you know so i'm doing the final
edit of what would the ancestors say look at all it's a lot of edits it's a lot of edits yeah
what it is um okay so here we are what would your ancestors say and so i'm going to invite someone
on stage on the camera to talk about their ancestry and where they think they're who they think they
are where they think they are where they think where they think their ancestors would how they
think their ancestors would feel about where we are so let's see hold on let me turn my light hold
i'm sorry okay okay i'm here i'm here i was on i was on in the live yesterday too so i'm glad so you
know the vibe i know the vibe and i love it i love it this is right up my alley right now so
because my ancestors have been screaming we have oh my gosh we have gone past the part of
uh wait and see think about it take an extra 30 seconds so let's just wait and see you know see
how things play out and this whole past year i was told to be silent which is something i don't know
how to do well wait first of all before we even dive in what's your name and where you at uh my name
is sarah i am currently in washington state but i'm cali born and raised cali baby pasadena
all past okay all right all right all right so talk to us so these ancestors are screaming at
you they told you to shut up yes for a whole year uh and i'm seeing the benefits of it now
because by being silent um i really got to see how things played out so wait i want to know first
did it did you is this the first time they told you to be silent yes and you listened yes what
made you so obedient uh so my mom is uh my aunt is my mom she raised me okay and she was never one
to be silent okay she was like hey if someone messed with you you say something she would take
me to school listening to sugar free okay okay if you know you know if you know you know if you know
you know and she would say if any girl messes with you um these are the comebacks that you use
got you okay okay because who's gonna argue with comebacks from sugar free you can use tupac if you
want to and i love me some tupac don't get me wrong yes but who's gonna you know who's gonna you know
come at you with some sugar free stuff and so um my grandmother who is also my mom's mother but
uh i was so angry with her because of who my dad was and who he became okay because that's where my
trauma came from yeah and it was so confusing to see those two my dad and my aunt who raised me but
they were two different people and so she started kind of popping in through meditation i write poetry
i have a book as well thank you yeah i call it the disc book to my daddy it's called jonathan drinking
music and she just kept popping in but i would hear her as like my mom and it was so again so
confusing and she would just sit there and stare at me and it would bug me but it worked right and so
then she was the one who told me to be silent and because spite is my motivation right
i was like bet because you made my daddy who he was in my mind right um i'm gonna do what you say
so that way when things don't work out which they did i could just go full blast on your ass because
you ruined my daddy and you also took my mama from me she died 10 years ago from a heart attack
just like my grandmother generational curses and all all that stuff right i get this new job in
washington state full of white people i'm the only black woman up in there and when i tell you
it felt like i was in slavery times why with the microaggressions with the gas lighting it even had
me thinking like did i do something like what happened i was quiet i did everything i was told
and then april i got shingles i'm 36 not shingles yes and i'm like dang and i don't want kids that's
stress yeah and i don't want kids never been pregnant i'm like is this my karma for
is this what childbirth is me with generational oh my god you i was going through it and it took
me a whole month not to realize what it was because you know i was like there's no way i have shingles
i'm 36 finally go to the er i couldn't walk okay and then as soon as the shingles was over i hear
my grandmother billy jean bolden go do it i'm like do what she was like aren't you a poet
don't you got the gift of gab what's your daddy teach you what's all those legalese that your
daddy teach you where do you think he learned it from but who taught you how to say it your mama
my daughter your auntie the woman who raised you who didn't have to raise you
i was like okay and so we played and i should we played around with it she was like don't and the
number one thing she told me when i went back into that office she was like don't make it personal
it's personal but don't make it personal use your brain so this is all this is all conversations
that are happening where like in dreams in dreams meditation through my poetry everywhere through
music hands down through music and so i'm like all right so i test out little things here and there
so i'll i would say something like didn't we mention this yesterday didn't we mention that
yesterday because a black woman speaking up is automatically a problem even if you're if you're
nice about it and so she was like remember uh something about receipts isn't that something y'all
be saying ain't that not you and grandma hanging out baby and because she knew because the anger i had
was similar to my dad's where he had so much respect for her but he was so angry with her
same thing with my dad i had so much respect for him my dad was not the best person but when it came
to handling some business he could handle it he got it done okay i have a sister i have a sister who's
16 years younger than me and that man had to represent himself for both of our custody cases
solo dolo no lawyer and one wow that's impressive as a black man
so that's that's where she was like kind of like putting the legalese like you were there
you heard it you know you was you was there i was there and so i was like okay so she was like
use your gift of gab that your dad taught you but use legal terms and receipts and time stamps is the
number one way not only that just don't focus on what the legal terms are find the loopholes as
black people as black women we have to learn the loopholes to use to our advantage so she's like you
got your mama who was born in the in the 60s you got me who was born in what 1930s or something like
that let's combine them let's combine 2025 with 1950s in the 1930s because we gonna teach you what the
slaves have been telling us baby when i honestly i'm mostly impressed that you listened me too
because i feel like that's like were you always tapped in like this no no no no no my uh my mom
died 10 years ago and it took me up into uh 13 oh yeah 10 years uh it took it took me almost five
years to really pay attention because i wanted to take my own life i wanted to be with her
i couldn't take it no more i could not take it no more and not just because i didn't want to be
here no more i became my father's caretaker and so him being an alcoholic was gone and i had to see
his true colors and we just started tearing at each other tearing each other apart which led to that
anger towards her even more because it's just like oh it's not just the alcohol that made him this way
this is what he really is but it was also my deniability i didn't want to believe my dad was this terrible
person um and so i moved away i ran away my family don't even know that i'm in washington state
they were gonna find out now they about to fight my dad know he got a book named after him though
and the uh the introduction piece is a disletter to him no i get it i get it and my second book is uh
now titled is going to be uh inner demons and affirmations to speak about this because just
like black people especially black women we are taught these things to survive in a society that
hates us every community that hates us and so i had to break that apart and relearn it while i'm
learning it and learning how to use it now while being in a white ass state the iron the irony of it
all and me coming to washington was a pure accident i was in oregon before this which is even worse
so i had to look at that i was like so if i'm here and not people like me at all and especially
people where i'm at don't like me at all there has to be something to this and the fact that my
grandmother of all people more than my mother kept popping up within this last year it just kept
telling me you need to pay attention to this because now that i'm seeing everything that i was taught
was for survival and i'm grateful for that but she also taught them that right and she saw things
worse than i did worse than my mama worse than my daddy yeah so let's connect the two and i'm so
grateful that my aunt raised me because i'm half ethiopian no nothing about the ethiopian people none of
that stuff i was there for the first five years of my life and i see the the disconnect between
africans who come to america and african americans yeah i mean that's the bridge you know like these
coalitions have to get built um and there's i believe like for instance because i am grenadian
and from the u.s like in both very authentic ways that it like those of us who are from these different
spaces of the diaspora like we have to be bridges and part of that is going to come from reaching
back to the the the ancestry from these different spaces and bringing it forward so i hear you yeah
definitely and the traditions i do love some of them i do remember and i understand but now i see
how that plays a role into into capitalism white supremacy while living in a white state and so
literally by just being silent and paying attention and listening to her but also my mom was my
confirmation so anytime i was like i don't know this sounds either a little too too dark or a little
too good to be true and this is something she just told me recently six months ago she was like never
feel bad for advocating for yourself no never and i was like oh my gosh it was something i knew in my
heart but i had to hear it from her i couldn't hear it from nobody else but i had to hear it from her
and with listening and paying attention and meditation with the last five years and everything that's
happening instead of just hearing my mom as this mystical angel like she's at peace now
i could literally hear her like every day when i get home from school or work going
that's my that's my nickname and i'm like that's you mama it's you that's you because it's her voice
it's not just this soft-spoken thing and she was like didn't i tell you to stop you never feel bad for
advocating for yourself i've been waiting to shout from the rooftops you know how long i've been wanting
to cuss motherfuckers out that's amazing that's really i mean it's not simply just affirming in
you advocating for yourself but would you say that it's also helped with your grief oh so much so
so much so now when um she has a funeral song that i used to avoid uh stevie wonder sherry amore
and yeah and now when i hear it i'm like oh because it's um when he's talking about maybe
you'll see me from a distant cloud and i'm just like oh is that what you're trying to tell me when
i was boohoo crying this entire time and she's like yeah and then when he says i wish you were mine
and she's like yeah and you're my daughter but i wish you were like biologically like i wish i had
birthed you but now seeing you in these last 10 years i didn't realize how much you were paying
attention to me she was like i was just trying to make sure you didn't turn out like your punk ass
daddy that's all i was doing so it has helped so much with my grief and it has helped me understand
myself better but all the different parts of me as a black woman you know um most will call me
racially ambiguous i don't see it but that's how everybody else sees oh my gosh i don't know how many
times people be like where are you from and i'll be like i can see people thinking you're indian i can see
yeah but everywhere i go it's like where are you from i'm from here where's your family from
yeah but your family is from other places it is but i'm not gonna tell you that because i do
when i tell people i'm ethiopian especially other black people immediately i can see the switch up
yeah oh you're not black black you know or it's like you talk black or you you sound black and then
when i say i'm ethiopian it's like they get all prim and proper oh interesting and i'm just like
no no no no no sweetie that's not how it works okay and then a lot of times black men would want
to date me because i that's basically how i came to be uh because my daddy loves black women but he likes
uh what is it what's this phrase that they say exotics exotics there we go exotic black women right
thank you thank you exotic and so when black men would try to date me and then i would tell them like
no baby i'm really black and then they hear me actually talk like cuss their ass out again the switch
up happens and so it's like you you're showing me that you don't like black women which means i
can't i can't be with you sir because if you don't like black women you don't like me and it doesn't
i don't care if you don't like me but it also means you don't like your mama how can i date a man who
don't like their mama here's the thing about not lighting not liking moms you cannot like this is
what i've understood i feel like the men that i've known it's not the issue isn't that they
don't like their mom it's that they don't like that they don't like their mom exactly so you end
up having to deal with the resentment that they have for themselves as well as the resentment they
have for their mom and they haven't worked through that so now they working it out on you and that's
been the whole 36 years of my life with my punk ass daddy and i love that man when i say that it's
because my mama says it all the time so now it's ingrained into my head and she's even like who do you
think gave you the title of your book she was like i'm gonna you wrote the poems you wrote them
you know you were trying to be you know edgar allen poe and do something poetic with your book you
know to seem important and you know which is fine and she was like but but but but who pisses you off
the most i was like my dad and she was like and what are you both like doing drinking i don't do that
no more um and she was like and what do you guys bond over the most that's how you guys connected
the most i was like music i learned music from him and how to dissect it how to learn the words
um because he was also he i'm dyslexic he's dyslexic but he's dyslexic with words i'm dyslexic with
numbers what's it called when you're dyslexic with numbers i don't i think it should be dyslexia
no it's like calculexia or something like that i don't know i really feel like i have that because
they keep they keep changing the names i don't even know everything's a spectrum there's a specific
word for number dyslexia where you flip because i do that all the time so i feel like i got that
i think i think the older you get too though because even now i flip certain words because they either
sound the same or they mean the same and so because i've been in school of life my entire life
and there's so much happening up here i automatically will it's normal just to confuse the words especially
when it sounds the same but isn't dyslexia that like it's it's on the page that you're flipping it
it's also it's on the page but it's also uh auditory oh i didn't know that yeah it's auditory um and
the reason why i figured this out for myself is because um i went to school for a stenographer school
oh okay and uh you definitely got to hear the words as they come out to do that
you definitely do and it's shorthand it's a 10 key uh machine right and then it transcribes into a
word document so you have the machine hooked up to a laptop and it turns into a word document like a
regular word document yeah and so um i could tell the difference between the two so let's say
uh the word you is spelled s-t-p-h i think and then o-u on the stenographer thing and then you
and it goes into the word document but i could visually see the difference between the two but
sometimes when i would hear it i would confuse it oh interesting
mm-hmm okay so where do you what do you think um what do you think your grandma would say about
where the world is now right now and let me just tell y'all your comments have not been scrolling so
i can't see anybody's comments because instagram is hating uh i do instagram lives a lot and there's
a lot of glitches and that's been happening a lot no this is shadow banning oh and then also too
it's showing me that the comments are like it shows comments off i can't even comment if i want
to the comments are very much on yeah um that's the best part because because of going back and
seeing everything and having multiple generations talk to me because it's now just not my mother and
grandmother um what they're saying is baby get ready for the ride of revenge and not for us and i'm not
saying for black people i'm saying for people who's been paying attention and dissecting everything
and the number one thing that has been popping up for me is for me and everybody else um is
do inventory of the last seven years of your life okay everything good bad and ugly right then apply it to
current events okay and what those current events mean to you uh-huh and then you will not only see
what karma you may receive personally but the karmic justice we are all about to see because they keep
recreating the same spell that they did 400 years ago yes and it's not working because the ancestors
have full range on this land and soil and not just america baby globally globally because it's all
connected right so like my the racism i experience it we all have racism right but mine is specifically
catered to me for my environment experience and the people i have been around and because of history
and everybody else in this room in the comments right so how that applies to me and everybody else is
going to transform into reality meaning we are going to get our karma especially if we've been
waiting for many on the sidelines hoping praying and fighting and all kinds of stuff even if we've
been wrong because you have to be wrong in order to get it right so we are going to see the evolution
of that because because everything is energy energy cannot be destroyed nor created right and so no matter
who you believe in the whoever you think is wicked they got so many chances while we were waiting on
the sidelines hoping praying manifesting yes creating books making diss poems about our parents
and forgiving forgiveness we are now going to it's uh i know people have been talking about destiny
swapping but it is going to be a destiny swap because the people who hurt you and went against you
got their blessings and manifestations but shitted on it weren't grateful weren't grateful for that's a
whole other life baby okay so now we are going to receive that back because everything is about
balance so if a bunch of us have been in balance while trying to maintain the balance while holding
on to our humanity no matter who we are we are going to get that back and then some there's a phrase
i think it's a saying um everything taken from me will return back to me multiplied and some
people it's going to be negative it's going to be ugly it's going to be dark and for everyone who's
been in that darkness been trying to get out of it it's about to get so good and it's going to be in
the details the tiny tiny tiny details and that's what's about to happen and if you don't believe it now
right because current events right just keep watching those current events put the pieces together
and you're going to see the end result and what we decide as people to do with that end result
is going to determine what happens next for us in our karma do you want to continue to be silent and
fearful or do you want to do you want to thrive and be triumphant even in this cruel wicked world
because everything that we're seeing right now it's already happened a thousand times yes more than a
400 years all that other whatever everybody want to talk about and believe in so if you have been
trying to manifest a family community right but specifically catered to you and what your passion
is not what you want your passion and your desires that's what we're all about to get and people desire
evil wicked things and we're gonna see that come out to play and i'm so excited because i was silent as
well too so well i can't wait to see it thank you so much for sharing with us this was i feel like
every time people come on it's just i love seeing how different everybody's stories are and congratulations
on your book that is a big feat and you know stay focused on staying connected because that seems to be
such a gift that so many of us don't have but the fact that you have it and then you get to bring
it forward through art is absolutely what you're supposed to be doing that's what purpose is
so thank you so much sarah i want to thank you before i drop down for you always being authentically
you even when it's not pretty because it helps me to be outspoken myself which is not easy being
outspoken is not easy no okay okay it's a purpose that is put onto us so i want to thank you because
when i have my dark days and you're not having a dark day it helps me get out of that dark day so i
can continue to be outspoken so thank you so much thank you bye bye
y'all we're so lucky to have this community here man i am also exhausted yes so we're only going to
have one guest tonight on what would your ancestors say but that guest was so fulfilling i mean i think
it's so fascinating when people are so are able to hear their ancestors so loud like in a very
specific fashion right like it's not even like she had to decode anything it was like i'm sitting
across the room from you telling you what to do but there's a certain level of belief and we and like
willingness to listen and receive that that there has to be in order to do so and so many people will
call themselves crazy before they listen to that they'll be like oh like i'm bugging you know um
or you may think that you're not hearing your grandest your ancestors you may think that you're
hearing some like inner voice within you that is harmful to you and that's some of the work that you
do in therapy right like that's some of the work that you do in meditation is getting to understand
what are the voices that you're hearing are these voices from your childhood that are grounded in like
the negativity are these voices of doubt that you receive from outside sources are these voices of
energy that are coming from the connectivity that you have to something that is otherworldly like
that type of shit is not just like some easy peasy stuff that you just kind of land in for most people
like you have to actually work at that and that tastes like being quiet and still and a lot of people
ain't trying to do that neither so um remember my show what would the ancestors say and book go to
amandaseales.com and support you know it's really um exciting to just see that folks are not taking
this lightly and you know because every time i do something i'm always afraid like okay are people
going to really get what i'm doing or understand where i'm coming with it and to see you all like
really earnestly supporting is is very um affirming to me so remember if you are in la you can come see
the show live if you're in la and um that would be the in studio tickets and then if you are in um
another city and you can't join live then you can always get the live stream tickets and we have
different live stream tickets we have live stream tickets for just the live stream but then we also have
a live stream bundle that comes with the signed book okay so i know people are looking at looking
for that so want to make sure that you guys know that that's available to you and um you know that
you support your girl support your girl um i cannot even front i am so super dupes tired i'm gonna leave you
an entire this pictureたling and i am so proud to talk to you so that you want to make sure that you can
see you anyway